pobox.com 2012-05-25

# Pobox.com Privacy Policy

This policy covers how IC Group treats personal information that we collect and receive through our Pobox.com and Listbox.com web sites. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Advertising** We do not sell advertising space on any of our websites. You may see notices about our own products, but we do not use your eyeballs to make money.

We also do not distribute ads by email, either to Pobox subscribers or through our mailing lists. We do not even tell you about our own products, unless you have asked us to, or there is a change that will affect, or has affected, your service (recent examples include changes to SMTP service).

**Your Personal Information** When you register with us, we ask for your name, mailing address, telephone number, and a security question of your choosing. We collect, store, and use this personal information to confirm your identity when you contact us, and to contact you regarding your account. That's it.

If you do not provide that information accurately, you reduce our ability to confirm your identity as the account holder. If you feel very strongly about this matter, we urge you to fill in as much as possible, and select a strong security question and answer (in [the Personal Information section of the User's Area](http://pobox.com/login/mason/change-question/)) and to **remember the answer**. IC Group is not liable for any changes made to your account as a result of our inability to confirm your identity.

Because we do not derive income from advertising, we do not aggregate your personal information for marketing purposes. However, we may use your data to determine some basic information about our user base (for example, how many customers do we have in a particular country.)

We do not sell, loan, lease, give away, share or in any other way make your personal information or your Pobox address available to parties other than IC Group, Inc. and its affiliates, except:

  * when you have given us permission (example: to deal with another company on your behalf);
  * when you have violated our [Terms of Service](http://www.pobox.com/user-agreement), and misused your Pobox account for spam or other prohibited uses;
  * in the event of a merger or a transfer of all or substantially all our assets to a third party, provided that we will notify you before personal information becomes subject to a different privacy policy; and
  * to comply with law or legal process (subpoenas), or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

If your information has been subpoenaed from us, you will be informed unless we are specifically barred from doing so by the subpoena.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information** You can access and edit your account information at any time (in fact, we encourage you to keep this information up to date, so that we do not we try to call you and find the phone number disconnected). Your personal information can be edited at [the Personal Information section of the User's Area.](https://www.pobox.com/login/mason/change-info/)

Your account can be canceled at any time by going to <http://www.pobox.com/home/cancel/>, responding to invoices with "cancel", or by contacting our Customer Service staff at [pobox@pobox.com](mailto:pobox@pobox.com "Send an email to Pobox
    Support"). If you ask us to delete your account, your account will usually be deactivated and we will stop accepting mail for your addresses within 1 hour. Please note that information may remain in back-up storage for some further period of time. 

**Security** We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you; however we cannot guarantee that someone won't be able to circumvent these safeguards. These safeguards include, but are not limited to, mandating password protection for all accounts, confirming that a request to send personal information or passwords to email addresses not listed in an account was submitted by a person authorized to do so for that account, encrypting credit card and password information within our system, and taking measures to protect our servers, databases and other system components against intrusions, tampering, and other attacks.

**Information We Store - Pobox Basic and Pobox Plus** We do not store messages coming through our servers for forwarding accounts. Once we receive a message, we immediately attempt to process it, and send it to your forwarding address. We will keep that message in the following cases:

  1. There is a problem with your forwarding address. We will attempt to resend the message for a maximum of 5 days.
  2. You have set your email or spam filters to discard the message. We will keep the message for 30 days, in case you discarded something you wanted. Discards may also be used to tune the spam filters.

**Information We Store — Pobox Mailstore** We store messages coming through our servers for Mailstore accounts. Messages are stored until you delete them or your account has reached its quota, at which point new messages will not be stored.

If your account is terminated, your messages will be stored for an additional 30 days, then deleted at the same time your account settings are deleted.

**Cookies** We use cookies. Why? It's the simplest way, technically, to allow you to use our website. We know that it would be possible to run the site without cookies, but it is a needless complication. Here's what our cookies do:

  * If you check the box that says "Remember my username in the future", we put a cookie on your machine that does exactly that. It doesn't expire, because it would be useless if it did.
  * If you don't check that box, you will get a cookie once your password has been authorized. It will authorize your browser to make changes to your account for up to an hour, at which point it will expire.

We do not issue third-party cookies. You will receive cookies from one of these 3 domains or their subdomains: pobox.com, listbox.com and icgroup.com (our parent company.)

**Customer Service and System Maintenance** All messages sent to our customer service department are saved indefinitely, and become our property. If you contact Customer Service, we reserve the right to change your account settings or send email to your account in order to solve the problem. You may also receive test emails if we detect a problem with your account, even if you have not contacted us.

**Anonymity** Pobox.com is not an anonymous remailer. Your forwarding address may be revealed to your correspondents through bounce messages.

**Ownership Issues** All data, including emails, list content, subscriber lists and any list information disseminated through the Pobox.com or Listbox.com services, is the express property **of the account owner** and/or the author of a particular message.

**List Privacy** We do not make any information about our lists public. There is no system-wide database of lists. We do not provide listnames to people making inquiries. All of our privacy policies apply to your list subscribers as well as yourself.

**Information We Store - Listbox** All messages sent to lists are stored for the life of the list.

Subscription or other administrative requests sent via email are stored for 30 days.

**Children** Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to hold Pobox.com accounts and should not submit any personal information to us.

**Changes to the Policy** We reserve the right to update this privacy policy. If there are material changes, we will either notify you via e-mail or post notification prominently on our web site prior to implementing the changes. If you would like to receive notice via email, please go to [the Personal Information section of the User's Area](https://www.pobox.com/login/mason/change-info/), and specify that you would like to receive announcements from us.

**Contact Us** If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or there are any categories that you think we haven't covered, please let us know. We have tried to be as comprehensive as possible, but we'd like to know if we've missed anything. You can contact us [through our website](http://www.pobox.com/helpspot/index.php?pg=request), via email to [pobox@pobox.com](mailto:pobox@pobox.com "Send an
    email to Pobox Support"), or send us paper mail at:

IC Group, Inc.  
1100 Vine Street  
Suite C8  
Philadelphia, PA 19107
